let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What is the underlying technology behind cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin?",
      answer: "Blockchain",
      options: ["Artificial Intelligence", "Blockchain", "Quantum Computing", "Cryptographic algorithms"],
      
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Who is the pseudonymous creator of Bitcoin?",
      options: ["Satoshi Nakamoto", "Vitalik Buterin", "Charlie Lee", "Hal Finney"],
      answer: "Satoshi Nakamoto"
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "What is the term used to describe the process of verifying and adding transactions to the blockchain?",
      options: ["Mining", "Trading", "Forking", "Hodling"],
      answer: "Mining"
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which cryptocurrency introduced the concept of smart contracts?",
      options: ["Bitcoin", "Ethereum", "Ripple", "Litecoin"],
      answer: "Ethereum"
    },
    {numb: 5,
      question: "What is the maximum total supply of Bitcoin?",
      options: ["10 million", "21 million", "100 million", "1 billion"],
      answer: "21 million"
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "What consensus mechanism is primarily used by Ethereum?",
      options: ["Proof of Work (PoW)", "Proof of Stake (PoS)", "Delegated Proof of Stake (DPoS)", "Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT)"],
      answer: "Proof of Stake (PoS)"
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which cryptocurrency is known for its focus on privacy and anonymity?",
      options: ["Bitcoin", "Ethereum", "Monero", "Cardano"],
      answer: "Monero"
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the term used for a cryptocurrency that is pegged to the value of a fiat currency like the US dollar?",
      options: ["Stablecoin", "Altcoin", "Token", "ICO"],
      answer: "Stablecoin"
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is the name of the process by which new coins are created and distributed in a cryptocurrency network?",
      options: ["Mining", "Staking", "Minting", "Tokenization"],
      answer: "Mining"
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What is the purpose of a public key in cryptocurrency transactions?",
      options: ["To encrypt messages", "To verify signatures", "To generate addresses", "To initiate transactions"],
      answer: "To verify signatures"
    }
  ];
  
  // Example usage:
  console.log(cryptoQuestions[0].question); // Print the first question
  console.log(cryptoQuestions[0].options); // Print options for the first question
  console.log(cryptoQuestions[0].answer); // Print the answer for the first question
  